definitelyfilipino.com 2017-06-15

# Privacy Policy – Definitely Filipino™

**Your Privacy**

Definitely Filipino is committed to protecting your privacy. We will not sell or share your login information to anyone. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

When you register, we need to know your name and e-mail address. This allows us to identify the validity of your registration. Other than occasional notifications from our Administrator, your email and personal information will not be used for any other purpose.  We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.

**Will Definitely Filipino disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

Definitely Filipino does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Definitely Filipino may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

Definitely Filipino may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Definitely Filipino, our users, or others.

**In Summary**

Definitely Filipino is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make your visit at Definitely Filipino as enjoyable and informative as possible __. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Definitely Filipino also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and Definitely Filipino has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. Definitely Filipino cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

**Special Note About Google Advertising**

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.

To read more on Google’s Advertising & Privacy policy, and/or to opt out of  interest-based advertising in web browsers, please visit Google’s Advertising & Privacy site by [clicking here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

**Questions and Feedback**

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, [please contact us](http://definitelyfilipino.com/blog/index.php/contact-us).
